eatpig = [
    {"question":"彷彿","Answer":"páng fú"},
    {"question":"跨越","Answer":"kuàyuè"},
    {"question":"美洲大陸","Answer":"měizhōu dàlù"},
    {"question":"威斯康辛州","Answer":"wēisīkāngxīn zhōu"},
    {"question":"木造","Answer":"mùzào"},
    {"question":"現今","Answer":"xiànjīn"},
    {"question":"居住","Answer":"jūzhù"},
    {"question":"大廈林立","Answer":"dàshà línlì"},
    {"question":"東京","Answer":"dōngjīng"},
    {"question":"截然不同","Answer":"jiéránbùtóng"},
    {"question":"木工師傅","Answer":"mùgōng shīfù"},
    {"question":"嗅","Answer":"xiù"},
    {"question":"遼闊","Answer":"liáokuò"},
    {"question":"聽說","Answer":"tīng shuō"},
    {"question":"平均","Answer":"píngjūn"},
    {"question":"計算","Answer":"jìsuàn"},
    {"question":"自作主張","Answer":"zì zuòzhǔ zhāng"},
    {"question":"計算","Answer":"jìsuàn"},
    {"question":"扣掉","Answer":"kòudiào"},
    {"question":"福島","Answer":"fúdǎo"},
    {"question":"抵達","Answer":"dǐdá"},
    {"question":"一戶","Answer":"yīhù"},
    {"question":"周遭","Answer":"zhōuzāo"},
    {"question":"淨是","Answer":"jìng shì"},
    {"question":"浮","Answer":"fú"},
    {"question":"更","Answer":"gēng"},
    {"question":"何況","Answer":"hékuàng"},
    {"question":"住在","Answer":"zhù zài"},
    {"question":"毛骨悚然","Answer":"máogǔsǒngrán"},
    {"question":"即便","Answer":"jíbiàn"},
    {"question":"嚎叫","Answer":"háojiào"},
    {"question":"氣圍","Answer":"qìwéi"},
    {"question":"闖進","Answer":"chuǎngjìn"},
    {"question":"柵欄","Answer":"zhàlán"},
    {"question":"醃漬","Answer":"yānzì"},
    {"question":"煙燻","Answer":"yān xūn"},
    {"question":"話","Answer":"huà"},
    {"question":"腐壞","Answer":"fǔhuài"},
    {"question":"滲透","Answer":"shèntòu"},
    {"question":"各執一詞","Answer":"gèzhí yīcí"}
]